<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Melodies of a Dreamer</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">A Journey Through Music, Words, and Nature</string>
    <string name="article_text"><b>Melody in Her Heart</b>\n
        A young girl sits by her window wide,
        dreams in her eyes, a spark inside.
        The world hums soft, but she hears more,
        a symphony calling from her core.
        Her fingers dance on the keys so light,
        turning silence into day and night.
        Strings and notes in perfect grace,
        a melody her heart can\'t erase.
        Each song she sings, each tune she plays,
        carries her far in endless ways.
        In music\’s arms, she finds her flight,
        her soul aloft in pure delight.
        With every beat, her spirit soars,
        she finds herself and opens doors.
        For music\'s love will never end,
        a faithful guide, her closest friend.\n
        https://www.goodreads.com/series/350921-healing-hearts\n\n
    <b>Whispers of the Night</b>\n
        Beneath the stars, she finds her place,
        a world alive with notes that embrace.
        The night whispers secrets, soft and clear,
        and in her heart, the music draws near.
        With every strum of her guitar’s strings,
        a tapestry of dreams and hope it brings.
        The moonlight dances on her joyful face,
        as melodies weave through the quiet space.
        She sings of adventures, of love and of flight,
        her voice a beacon in the cool, still night.
        Each harmony carries her spirit away,
        to lands of wonder where she longs to stay.
        In the glow of the evening, her heart takes flight,
        guided by music, her soul shines bright.
        For in every rhythm, she finds her way,
        a lifelong companion, come what may.\n
        https://www.voicesofyouth.org/blog/whispers-night \n\n
    <b>The Arts of Words</b>\n
        In a quiet corner, she sits with grace,
        a journal open, lost in her space.
        <i>Words flow like rivers</i>, stories untold,
        painting her dreams in colors bold.
        The ink on the page dances and swirls,
        a canvas of thoughts for the young girl.
        With every line, her imagination flies,
        crafting new worlds beneath endless skies.
        She writes of adventures, of laughter and tears,
        of hopes and wishes, of all her fears.
        Each sentence a melody, each paragraph a song,
        in the symphony of life where she belongs.
        For in her writing, she finds her voice,
        a powerful whisper, a vibrant choice.
        The stories she tells become part of her heart,
        a magical journey, her own work of art.\n
        \n
        <b>Dancing with the Nature</b>\n
        With a gentle breeze, she steps outside,
        where flowers bloom and dreams collide.
        The sun spills warmth on her eager face,
        and nature’s melody fills the space.
        She twirls and dances on the vibrant grass,
        her laughter echoing as moments pass.
        The birds sing sweetly, the trees sway along,
        joining her spirit in a joyful song.
        Each step she takes is a note in the air,
        a celebration of life, a moment to share.
        She collects the whispers of the gentle wind,
        weaving them into stories that never end.
        For in this magic, her heart finds peace,
        a boundless adventure, a sweet release.
        With the world as her stage, she embraces the day,
        living in harmony, come what may.
    </string>
    <string name="redirect">Redirect</string>
</resources>